https://hbstudio.org/classes/registration-policies/privacy/

HB Studio - Privacy Policy | One of the Original Acting Studios in NYC
Workshops
Shakespeare’s MACBETH (Jonathan Lynn)
Contemporary Monologues (Clark Jackson)
Tennessee Williams’ CAMINO REAL: Scene Study (Austin Pendleton)
Online Auditions & Self Taping (Magaly Colimon)
The Language of Film (Ashish Pant)
Uta Hagen’s Acting Process 2 (Carol Rosenfeld)
Voice Over: Cartoons & Videogames (Theresa Buchheister & Ryan Downey)
Lorraine Hansberry Scene Study for Actors & Directors (Pat Golden)
Solo Show Incubator: Creating A Historic Character Icon (Janice Orlandi)
Acting on Camera for Teens (Portia)
Advanced Scene Study (Austin Pendleton)
Audition Technique: Contemporary Monologues (Paul Pryce)
Stop-Motion Animation for Actors (Howard Better)
Create Your Home Studio: Tech Basics for Actors & Directors (Pat Golden)
Voice Over Auditioning (Theresa Buchheister & Ryan Downey)
Scenes and Monologues (Michael Beckett)
Singing for Actors (Martha Bernard)
Scene Study: Script Analysis (Jessica Hecht)
Introduction to Shakespeare (Peter Francis James)
Acting in Accent: British RP (Theresa McElwee)
Advanced Shakespearean Acting (Peter Francis James)
Show Me the Money: Financial Empowerment for Artists (David M. Sharp)
Voice Over: Audiobooks (Theresa Buchheister & Ryan Downey)
Voice Over: Introduction (Jean-Marc Berne)
Privacy
Welcome to the HB Studio website. We are committed to protecting your privacy. Included below is our policy on how we handle any information we receive from you. You are not required to provide us with information in order to use this website. If you do not want us accessing and/or using your personal information as described herein, please do not provide us with any.
Policy Statement
HB Studio is committed to protecting the privacy of users of our site. The information summarized below explains to site users how we implement this protection in regard to information derived from this site.
Information Collection
We collect and save personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number and/or credit card number (collectively, “Personal Information”) that you provide to HB Studio in response to the forms on this site. We use your Personal Information only to communicate with people interested in HB Studio. We may from time to time distribute information to you through your email or mailing address on behalf of other similar organizations when we believe that you will find their information to be of interest. We never sell or rent your Personal Information.
Cookies
HB Studio employs “cookies” to provide better service to the visitors on this site. HB Studio does not use cookies to collect any personally identifying information from users or to track user activities beyond our site. HB Studio does not maintain copies of cookies on your site after you leave our site. Cookies are small pieces of temporary data that are exchanged between a web site and a user’s computer which enable a “session”, or “dialog” to be established between the two machines. With the session established, HB Studio is able to tailor its responses (i.e., identify and provide you with the information you want) and help you traverse our web pages in the most efficient and effective manner possible. The session is broken when our server does not receive further requests from your computer or you simply exit your browser. These cookies are normally deleted from a user’s computer when the user logs off the computer or the user exits the browser. In the event a cookie is found on your workstation, which was issued by the HB Studio server, you may remove it without adversely affecting your future visits to our site. You have the option of disabling cookies by accessing the tools provided to you in your Internet options. However, please note that you may not have full access to the website if you change your cookie settings to disable them.
Security
We are committed to using our best efforts to maintain the security of your Personal Information. When users submit Personal Information, the information is stored in a password-protected database on the HB Studio server. Where entry of a credit card account is required, that account information is only used to seek approval of the charge from your bank. [[Once the transaction is complete, no portion of the account information is retained or forwarded.]] The balance of the Personal Information is stored in our permanent records. Although we use our best efforts to protect the security of your Personal Information and our system, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, no transmission via the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of this and other factors beyond our control, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit to or through our Website. Therefore, you assume that risk by using the Website.
Information Usage
We use aggregate information collected by cookies to track site usage by volume. We use email addresses that people enter to send out our newsletter, to update people on HB Studio, to solicit donations, to distribute course offerings and other information concerning programs at HB Studio, and for other similar matters. We use donor records for tax purposes and periodic mailings soliciting donations. We use purchase records from course registrations to manage our course enrollments, determine popularity of courses and instructors, and distribute information about our course and event offerings and schedules. Contractors working on our site or mailing our newsletters or other communications may use the information under contract to us.
Opt-Out
If you do not want to receive email and/or mailings from us in the future, please let us know by sending email to us at the contact address below in the paragraph “How to Contact Us”, requesting to be removed from our email/mailing list. In addition to this, all email correspondence that we send you will include a link which when accessed by you, will enable you to remove yourself from our mailing lists. Please note that there might be a brief delay between when you submit your request to opt-out and when it is processed and reflected in our systems. Accordingly you might continue to receive communications from us for a limited time after you unsubscribe.
Links to Other Websites
This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you access any such third party links and to read the privacy policies of each website that you access. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by us.
Protection for Children
We have no intention of collecting personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, that child’s parent or legal guardian should contact us (see below) if they would like the information submitted by the child deleted from the website. We will delete such personally identifiable information from our database as soon as possible following our receipt of any such notice. If you are age 13 or younger, you are not authorized to submit any content or information to this website without the explicit consent of your parent or legal guardian.
Your Consent to this Privacy Policy
By using this site, you signify your assent to the HB Studio Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site or submit any Personal Information.
International Visitors
The laws and regulations in different countries impose different (and even conflicting) requirements on the Internet and data protection. HB Studio is located in the State of New York in the United States of America, as are the principal servers which make this site available worldwide. All matters relating to this site are governed by the laws of the State of New York in the USA. If you are located in a country other than the USA and you contact us, please note that any information you provide will be transferred to the USA and by submitting the information you authorize this transfer.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act Notice
HB Studio owns, protects and enforces copyright in its own creative materials and respects the copyright properties of others. Our site contains material of third parties and links to third party sites, portals and directories. As a result, materials of third parties, not owned or controlled by HB Studio, are included in or linked to our site. To the best of our knowledge, these materials do not infringe the copyrights of others. Upon receipt of notice of claimed infringement, HB Studio will respond expeditiously to follow the procedures specified in the Digital Millennium Copyright Act to resolve the claim between the notifying party and the alleged infringer who provided the materials in issue, including, where applicable, removing or disabling access to materials claimed to be infringing or by removing or disabling access to links to such material. It is the policy of HB Studio to terminate its relationships with third parties who infringe the copyrights of others where such parties are known to HB Studio to be repeat infringers. Any notice of claimed infringement should be sent to us in writing to the contact address below in the paragraph “How to Contact Us”.
Restrictions on Use
It is strictly prohibited to use or contact this site to disrupt or damage the site, its contents or its security measures or to harass or disparage HB Studio or our directors, officers or employees or our products or services or personnel or to interfere with the use and enjoyment of this site by other users. No unsolicited email (spam) may be directed by you to or through this site. You may not mirror any material contained on this site on any other server. You may not link to this site without HB Studio’s prior written permission. You may not frame or use framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of HB Studio without our prior written permission. You may not use any metatags or any other “hidden text” using HB Studio’s names or trademarks without our prior written permission. Links which appear on this site with our permission do not mean that we endorse the sites, products or services of the sponsors of the linked sites.
How to Contact Us
Should you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the collection and of information, please contact us:
HB Studio
120 Bank Street
New York, NY 10014
Tel: (212) 675-2370
Fax: (212) 675-2387
Email: info@hbstudio.org
Changes in our Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at our discretion. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post those changes here. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. If you continue to visit this website and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you will be deemed to have consented to the changes and will be subject to the revised Privacy Policy.
Copyright & Trademark
The content of this site is the property of HB Studio. No materials on this site may be reproduced, altered, or further distributed without the prior written permission of HB Studio. Copyright © HB Studio 2013; All Rights Reserved.
Share: Twitter Facebook Google+ Email
Classes
Acting
Acting 1
Acting 2
Acting with the Camera 1
Acting with the Camera 2
Acting with the Camera 3: Skill Integration for Film
Shakespeare’s MACBETH (Jonathan Lynn)
Contemporary Monologues (Clark Jackson)
Tennessee Williams’ CAMINO REAL: Scene Study (Austin Pendleton)
Online Auditions & Self Taping (Magaly Colimon)
The Language of Film (Ashish Pant)
Uta Hagen’s Acting Process 2 (Carol Rosenfeld)
Voice Over: Cartoons & Videogames (Theresa Buchheister & Ryan Downey)
Lorraine Hansberry Scene Study for Actors & Directors (Pat Golden)
Solo Show Incubator: Creating A Historic Character Icon (Janice Orlandi)
Acting on Camera for Teens (Portia)
Advanced Scene Study (Austin Pendleton)
Audition Technique: Contemporary Monologues (Paul Pryce)
Stop-Motion Animation for Actors (Howard Better)
Create Your Home Studio: Tech Basics for Actors & Directors (Pat Golden)
Voice Over Auditioning (Theresa Buchheister & Ryan Downey)
Scenes and Monologues (Michael Beckett)
Singing for Actors (Martha Bernard)
Scene Study: Script Analysis (Jessica Hecht)
Introduction to Shakespeare (Peter Francis James)
Acting in Accent: British RP (Theresa McElwee)
Advanced Shakespearean Acting (Peter Francis James)
Show Me the Money: Financial Empowerment for Artists (David M. Sharp)
Voice Over: Audiobooks (Theresa Buchheister & Ryan Downey)
Voice Over: Introduction (Jean-Marc Berne)
Follow HB Studio:
FacebookTwitterInstagramYouTubeRSS
Join our mailing list
Search for:
